Bruce Bassett papers relating to Jacques Lipchitz
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Film Projects Regarding Jacques Lipchitz, 1971-2001, Series 5:; (Boxes 10-34, 41-53, OV 57; 28.2 linear feet)
  - Original Footage and Stock Footage, 1971-1981, 5.1:
    For later filming in the US and Jerusalem, original camera reels, some with sound on film, and separate original sound reels are found. There is no paper record of these shoots in the collection. Material is arranged by subject and date. Other raw footage found includes four camera reels of sculptures by Lipchitz from the Metropolitan Museum.
    Other source material in this series includes stock footage and stock soundtrack, produced by others but used in Bassett's Lipchitz projects, and a couple of short reels of sound effects and titles.
    Note that the workprint is silent 16 mm picture unless otherwise indicated, original sound reels are ¼" tape, and soundtrack is 16mm fullcoat magnetic stock. Some of the later foundry and installation footage was shot on reversal positive film with a magnetic stripe soundtrack, identified in the container listing as sound on film.
    - Italy Filming (Box 10)
      - Script Book, circa 1971, (3 folders, photocopies) (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
      - Sound reels #1-14 and 25-49, 1971 August-September, (38 sound tape reels) (Box 11, Item 1-38)
      - Sound reels #50-71, 73-81, 107, 123-128, 1971, (38 sound tape reels) (Box 12, Item 1-38)
      - Sound Reels #129-166, 1971, (38 sound tape reels) (Box 13, Item 1-38)
      - Sound reels # 167-171, 1971, (5 sound tape reels) (Box 14, Item 1-5)
      - Dubbed sound reels #1-13, circa 1971, (13 sound tape reels) (Box 14, Item 6-18)
        (A key to original reels contained on each dub reel is found with dub reel 1, box 5, item 6.)
      - Interview of Lipchitz by Bruce Bassett, 1971 June 24, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 14, Item 19)
        (A pre-production interview, about the pending Metropolitan Museum exhibition)
      - Lipchitz Interview Re-takes, 1972 April 29, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 14, Item 20)
      - Interview with Jacques Lipchitz, circa 1971, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 14, Item 21)
        (Excerpts)
      - Florence Section Narration, undated, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 14, Item 22)
      - Lipchitz Working in Clay, Sync Sound, undated, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 14, Item 23)
      - Archival Reel 31, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 1)
        (Original camera reel 137)
      - Archival Reel 32, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 2)
        (Original camera reels 145-146)
      - Archival Reel 33, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 3)
        (Original camera reels 148-150)
      - Archival Reel 34, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 4)
        (Original camera reel 152)
      - Archival Reel 35, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 5)
        (Original camera reel 163)
      - Archival Reel 37, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 6)
        (Original camera reels 181-182)
      - Archival Reel 38, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 7)
        (Original camera reels 184-186)
      - Archival Reel 39, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 8)
        (Original camera reels 187-188)
      - Archival Reel 40, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 15, Item 9)
        (Original camera reels 189-191)
      - Archival Reel 41, circa 1971, (1 film reel: workprint picture) (Box 16, Item 1)
        (Original camera reels 192-193)
      - Archival Reel 31, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 2)
        (original sound reel 131)
      - Archival Reel 32, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 3)
        (Original sound reel 139-140)
      - Archival Reel 33, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 4)
        (Original sound reel 142-144)
      - Archival Reel 35, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 5)
        (Original sound reel 152)
      - Archival Reel 37, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 6)
        (Original sound reels 158-159)
      - Archival Reel 38, circa 1971, (1 film ree: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 7)
        (Original sound reels 162, 164)
      - Archival Reel 39, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 8)
        (Original sound reels 166-167)
      - Archival Reel 40, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 16, Item 9)
        (Original sound reels 167-169)
      - Archival Reel 41, circa 1971, (1 film reel: soundtrack) (Box 17, Item 1)
        (Original sound reels 170-171)
      - Lipchitz Working on His Sculpture The Last Embrace, circa 1972, (2 film reels: picture) (Box 17, Item 2)
    - Lipchitz Sculpture at the Metropolitan Museum, 1972, (4 film reels: picture; 2 oversized reels in Box 41) (Box 17, Item 3)
    - Index to Sculptures Filmed at the Metropolitan Museum, undated, (Index on paper, 1 folder) (Box 17, Item 4)
    - Selected Sculptures, European Shoot, undated, (1 videocassette: U-Matic) (Box 17, Item 5)
    - Philadelphia Installation and Dedication of Government of the People, 1976-1977, (16 film reels: picture, 2 film reels: sound on film, and 1 sound tape reel; film housed in 4 film cans, 2 oversized film cans in box 42) (Box 17, Item 6)
    - New York Installation of Bellerophon Taming Pegasus, 1977 April, (8 film reels: sound on film, 1 film reel: picture, 8 sound tape reels, 1 duplicate videocassette: U-Matic; film housed in 2 oversized film cans in box 43) (Box 18, Item 1)
    - Interview with Yulla Lipchitz, 1977 May, (5 film reels: picture; film housed in 2 film cans, 1 oversized film can in box 44) (Box 18, Item 2)
      (Picture only, no sound)
    - Italian Foundry Filming, 1977 August, (1 film reel: sound on film) (Box 18, Item 3)
    - Miami Interview with Joe Harrison, 1977, (1 film reel, 1 sound tape reel) (Box 18, Item 4)
      (See also series 5.2, Segments)
    - Israel Filming, 1977-1978, (8 film reels: picture, 1 film reel: sound on film; film housed in 2 film cans, 1 oversized film can in box 44) (Box 18, Item 5)
    - Unidentified Aerial Footage, undated, (1 film reel) (Box 18, Item 6)
    - Sound Effects and Titles, undated, (9 film reels: 35mm magnetic sound loop, 1 film reel: 16mm magnetic sound loop, 2 film reels: 35mm picture; film housed in 1 film can) (Box 18, Item 7)
    - Stills and Animation, undated, (5 film reels in 1 film can) (Box 18, Item 8)
    - Stock Footage, undated, (6 film reels in 1 film can) (Box 18, Item 9)
    - Oversized Reels of Original Footage, Lipchitz Sculpture at the Metropolitan Museum (from Box 17, item 3) (Box 41)
    - Oversized Film Cans of Original Footage, Philadelphia Installation (from Box 17, item 6) (Box 42)
    - Oversized Film Cans of Original Footage, New York Installation (from Box 18, item 1) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Film Cans of Original Footage, Yulla Lipchitz Interview and Israel Filming (from Box 18, items 2 and 5) (Box 44)
  - Jacques Lipchitz Interactive Project, 1972-2001, 5.2:
    This series contains the edited film and video created for the Lipchitz interactive project, as well as paper records documenting the production and presentation of its various installations.
    Audiovisual materials include multiple versions of "answers" compiled from the Lipchitz interviews filmed in 1971, used in multiple interactive installations between 1972 and 2001. Each version exists in a group of 2 to 4 reels or tapes, in its source format of motion picture film, or its installation format of various video types. Each group and its elements is described using the reel names and numbers assigned by Bassett to maintain their connection to paper documentation, and groups are arranged chronologically. Six miscellaneous reels, which do not appear to belong to any of the main groups of film reels, are arranged after the dated reels. Although they may duplicate some of the dated material, these miscellaneous reels were found to be in better condition than some of their copies, so they were retained.
    Also found are 117 small film and soundtrack reels of named segments whose titles correspond to segments listed in the source books. These may be outtakes or workprint of the edited Lipchitz answers.
    Paper records in this series include the original questions generated by the public during installations of the interactive project. Questions exist in multiple forms including orignal handwritten cards and printouts in multiple sets, each with a different arrangement of data. Notebooks include mainly technical and shot notes, but also notes on an Andy Goldsworthy interview. Production files contain detailed notes on the assembly of segments and revisions to the reels, including a negative pull list for a recent revision. The Program Guide contains annotated indexes to segments on each reel or disc, and other technical notes.
    Source Books, found in the paper documentation, provide a scene-by-scene content inventory and transcript of the audiovisual material in each version presented to the public between 1972 and 2001. They also contain notes related to the operation of the interactive program. Although all of the source books contain redundant and similar content, each version has its own annotations and a variety of interfiled production records specific to its particular installation. The 2001 source book from the Krannert Art Museum installation also includes a disc directory, photographs of sculptures in the Krannert exhibit, and an article on Lipchitz.
    Technical drawings show the way the video equipment was set up in the installations, showing a user in relation to the interactive system display. The Transcript folder includes a collection of Lipchitz's comments on Pablo Picasso gathered from the footage, a portion of which appears to have been licensed to another production company in the 1980s.
    The chronological arrangement of audiovisual materials in this series has been altered slightly due to the size and physical requirements of the objects.
    - Audiovisual Materials (Box 19)
      - Introduction, circa 1972, (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized workprint in box 45, oversized soundtrack in box 46) (Box 19, Item 1)
      - Birth-Cubism, circa 1972, (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized workprint in box 45, oversized soundtrack in box 46) (Box 19, Item 2)
      - Transparencies-Jacob and the Angel, circa 1972, (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized soundtrack in box 46, oversized workprint in box 47) (Box 19, Item 3)
      - Mother-Virgin, circa 1972, (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized workprint in box 47, oversized soundtrack in box 48) (Box 19, Item 4)
      - Reel A, Part 1, 1972, (2 film reels: A+B roll, 1 sound tape reel) (Box 19, Item 5)
      - Reel A, Part 2, 1972, (2 film reels: A+B roll, 1 sound tape reel) (Box 19, Item 6)
      - Reel B, Part 1, 1972, (2 film reels: A+B roll, 1 sound tape reel) (Box 19, Item 7)
      - Reel B, Part 2, 1972, 1981, (2 film reels: A+B roll, 1 sound tape reel) (Box 19, Item 8)
      - Unidentified Reel, 1972, (2 film reels: A+B roll) (Box 20, Item 1)
      - Reel D, 1979, (2 videocassettes: U-Matic, 1 with visible time code) (Box 20, Item 2)
      - Reels A-D, 1979, (4 videocassettes: Betacam SP) (Box 21, Item 1)
      - Discs I-II, circa 1982, (2 videocassettes: U-Matic) (Box 21, Item 2)
      - Discs I-IV, 1999, (4 videocassettes: Digital Betacam) (Box 21, Item 3)
      - Reel A, 1982, (2 film reels: workprint, 2 film reels: soundtrack) (Box 22, Item 1)
      - Reel B, 1982, (2 film reels: workprint, 2 film reels: soundtrack) (Box 22, Item 2)
      - Reel C, 1982, (1 film reel: workprint, 1 film reel: soundtrack; oversized workprint in Box 49, oversized soundtrack reel in Box 48) (Box 22, Item 3)
      - Reel D, 1982, (1 film reel: workrpint, 1 film reel: soundtrack; oversized workrpint in Box 49, oversized soundtrack reel in Box 48) (Box 22, Item 4)
      - Miscellaneous Reels (Box 23)
        - Monitor Station Segments, undated, (2 film reels: internegative and answer print, 1 sound tape reel) (Box 23, Item 1)
        - Met, undated, (2 film reels: workprint and sountrack) (Box 23, Item 2)
        - Reel C, Part 1, undated, (1 film reel: workprint) (Box 23, Item 3)
          (Note on original can: "does not contain Picasso")
        - Q+A Reel C, 1971, (1 film reel: picture, oversized reel in box 50) (Box 23, Item 4)
        - Reel II, Part 1, undated, (1 film reel: picture, oversized reel in box 50) (Box 23, Item 5)
          (Leader also labeled "D Reel")
        - Unidentified Reel, undated, (1 film reel: workprint) (Box 23, Item 6)
      - Segments (Box 23)
        - Art Is Eternal, Banker's Economy, Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981, (4 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 23, Item 7)
        - Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981, (6 film reels: workprint, in 2 film cans) (Box 23, Item 8)
        - Birth and Unity, circa 1971-1981, (3 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 1)
        - Columbine, circa 1971-1981, (2 film reels: workprint, in 1 oversized film can in box 51) (Box 24, Item 2)
        - Cubism, End Section, FF, First Come to America, Florence, Freeze, Government of the People, circa 1971-1981, (7 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 3)
        - Government of the People, circa 1971-1981, (3 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 4)
        - Gursenski, James Joyce, circa 1971-1981, (4 film reels: workprint) (Box 24, Item 5)
        - Last Embrace, circa 1971-1981, (4 film reels: workprint, in 1 oversized film can in box 51) (Box 24, Item 6)
        - Man Getting Better, Miami and Joe Harrison Interview, circa 1971-1981, (4 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 7)
        - Miami and Joe Harrison Interview, Mother and Child, Notre Dame de Liesse, circa 1971-1981, (5 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 8)
        - New Segments, Opening, Paracelles, Pollution Affects Art, Storytelling, circa 1971-1981, (7 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 9)
        - Yulla Lipchitz/Israel, circa 1971-1981, (6 film reels: workprint, in 1 oversized film can in box 52) (Box 24, Item 10)
        - Unidentified Segments, circa 1971-1981, (7 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 11)
      - Miscellaneous Trims, circa 1971-1981, (workprint and soundtrack in 1 film can) (Box 24, Item 12)
      - Segments, continued (Box 25)
        - Art Is Eternal, Banker's Economy, Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981, (5 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 1)
        - Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981, (4 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 2)
        - Birth and Unity, circa 1971-1981, (4 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 3)
        - Birth and Unity, Cubism, FF, First come to America, circa 1971-1981, (5 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 4)
        - Gursenski, James Joyce, Last Embrace, circa 1971-1981, (6 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 5)
        - Man Getting Better, Miami and Joe Harrison, circa 1971-1981, (3 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 6)
        - New Segments, Notre Dame de Liesse, Pollution Affects Art, Storytelling, circa 1971-1981, (6 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Box 25, Item 7)
        - New Segments, Transparencies/Jacob and the Angel, Yulla/Israel, circa 1971-1981, (6 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 oversized film can in Box 52) (Box 25, Item 8)
        - Unidentified Segments, circa 1971-1981, (13 film reels: soundtrack, in 2 film cans) (Box 25, Item 9)
    - Demonstrations (Box 26)
      - Metropolitan Museum, 1972 June 11, (1 sound tape reel) (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - City University of New York, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Exxon Education Foundation, 1979, (2 folders, script and 1 videocassette: U-Matic) (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
    - Exhibition Materials (Box 26)
      - Magnetic Strips, circa 1971-2001, (in shoebox) (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Segment Boards, circa 1972-2001, (oversized item in OV 57) (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Signs, circa 1972-2001, (oversized item in OV 57) (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Topic Cards, circa 1972-2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Production Notebooks, circa 1999 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Production Files, circa 1972-2001, (4 folders) (Box 26, Folder 10-13)
    - Program Code, circa 1999, (2 folders) (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
    - Program Guide, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Questions and Answers (Box 27)
      - Handwritten Question Cards, circa 1972, (6 folders) (Box 27, Folder 1-6)
      - Printouts of All Questions, 1973, (2 folders) (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
      - Printouts of Questions with Answers, 1973, (4 folders) (Box 27, Folder 9-12)
      - Printed Questions on Sorting Cards, circa 1973, (3 folders) (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
      - Annotated Questions, circa 1972-2001, (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
      - Coded Questions, circa 1972-2001, (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Source Books (Box 28)
      - 1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - circa 1973 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - 1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - 1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - circa 1998 (Box 28, Folder 9-11)
      - circa 2000 (Box 28, Folder 12-14)
      - Krannert Art Museum, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
      - Reels A-D and Parts I and II Revised Script, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Technical Drawings of Interactive System, circa 1972-2001 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Transcript of Picasso Segment, circa 1972-2001 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Introduction (workprint from Box 19, item 1) (Box 45)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Birth-Cubism (workprint from box 19, item 2) (Box 45)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Introduction (soundtrack from Box 19, item 1) (Box 46)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Birth-Cubism (soundtrack from box 19, item 2) (Box 46)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Transparencies-Jacob and the Angel (soundtrack from Box 19, item 3) (Box 46)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Transparencies-Jacob and the Angel (workprint from box 19, item 3) (Box 47)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Mother-Virgin (workprint from Box 19, item 4) (Box 47)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Mother-Virgin (circa 1972) (soundtrack from Box 19, item 4) (Box 48)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Reel C (1982) (soundtrack from Box 22, item 3) (Box 48)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Reel D (1982) (soundtrack from Box 22, item 4) (Box 48)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Reel C (1982) (workprint from Box 22, item 3) (Box 49)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Reel D (1982) (workprint from Box 22, items 4) (Box 49)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Miscellaneous Reels, Q+A Reel C (from box 23, items 4) (Box 50)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Miscellaneous Reels, Reel II, Part 1 (from box 23, item 5) (Box 50)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Segments, Columbine (workprint, from Box 24, item 2) (Box 51)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Segments, Last Embrace (workprint, from Box 24, item 6) (Box 51)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Segments, Transparencies-Jacob-Yulla (workprint, from Box 24, item 10) (Box 52)
    - Oversized Audiovisual Materials, Segments, New Segments, Transparencies-Jacob, Yulla (soundtrack, Box 25, item 8) (Box 52)
    - Oversized Exhibition Materials, Segment Board and Signs (from Box 26, items 6-7) (Box 57)
  - Jacques Lipchitz Documentary, 1972-1994, 5.3:
    This series contains audiovisual and a few paper records related to the documentary Bassett produced about Jacques Lipchitz. The first version was created in 1972 in tandem with the Metropolitan Museum of Art's Lipcthiz retrospective exhibition. The documentary was updated in 1977 with footage added from the posthumous large-scale sculpture installations, and then revised again in 1991.
    The series includes multiple finished versions of the documentary in their presentation and distribution formats (film and video), and pre-print master elements of the finished versions (A+B roll and internegative; master from which distribution copies are made). Also found are production elements made at different stages of production and revision, excerpts of the finished film compiled for publicity, and two pieces of television coverage of the installation of Bellerophon Taming Pegasus that use Bassett's footage.
    Some of the film cans contain paper lab records for prints and edits created over the years.
    Additional records related to the documentary are found in Series 2.1 Business Records, Jacques Lipchitz Art Foundation, and Series 3, Printed Materials.
    One copy of the documentary has been digitized for research use.
    - Finished Versions (Box 29)
      - Presentation Copies (Box 29)
        - circa 1972, (2 videocassettes: U-Matic) (Box 29, Item 1)
        - 1977, (2 film reels) (Box 29, Item 2)
        - 1977, 1983, (2 duplicate videocassettes: U-Matic) (Box 30, Item 1)
        - Short Version1989, 1990, (1 film reel and 2 duplicate videocassettes: U-Matic and VHS; oversized film reel housed in Box 53) (Box 30, Item 2)
        - 1991, (1 film reel and 2 duplicate videocassettes: U-Matic and VHS; oversized film reel housed in Box 53) (Box 30, Item 3)
      - Pre-Print Master Elements (Box 31)
        - Reel 1, 1972, 1974, (4 film reels: A+B Roll picture and 2 soundtrack reels) (Box 31, Item 1)
          (Can with A Roll contains film lab records)
        - Reel 2, 1972, 1974, 1976, (4 film reels: sound effects tracks A-D) (Box 31, Item 2)
        - Reel 2, 1972, 1974, 1976, (8 film reels: A+B Roll picture and 6 unmixed soundtrack reels) (Box 32, Item 1)
        - Reels 1 and 2, 1976, 1978-1980, (4 film reels: internegative picture and soundtrack) (Box 33, Item 1)
        - Reel 1, 1991, (2 film reels: internegative picture and soundtrack) (Box 33, Item 2)
    - Production Elements (Box 33)
      - Original Ending, circa 1972, (9 film reels: A+B Roll picture, internegative picture and soundtrack, and answer print, housed in 2 film cans) (Box 33, Item 3)
      - Revised Ending, 1977, (2 sound tape reels) (Box 33, Item 4)
      - Parts I, II, and III, circa 1977, (3 sound tape reels) (Box 33, Item 5)
      - Titles, 1977, (1 film reel) (Box 33, Item 6)
      - Pre-print with Visible Time Code, 1991, (3 videocassettes: U-Matic) (Box 34, Item 1)
    - Excerpts (Box 34)
      - Two Segments: Bellerophon Taming Pegasus, Freedom of Expression, circa 1977, (1 videocassette: U-Matic) (Box 34, Item 2)
      - Stills and Segments for Random House Presentation, 1994, (1 videocassette: Betacam SP) (Box 34, Item 3)
    - Television Coverage (Box 34)
      - Today Show, 1977 June 16, (1 film reel, 1 duplicate videocassette: U-Matic, film reel housed in Box 53) (Box 34, Item 4)
      - News Story on Bellerophon Taming Pegasus Installation, 1977, (1 film reel, 1 duplicate videocassette: U-Matic, film reel housed in Box 53) (Box 34, Item 5)
        (Film can contains film lab records)
    - Finished Versions, Presentation Copies, 1989 and 1991 (2 film reels from Box 30, items 2-3) (Box 53)
    - Television Coverage, Today Show (from Box 34, item 4) (Box 53)
    - Television Coverage, News Story on Bellerophon Taming Pegasus Installation (from Box 34, item 5) (Box 53)
- Other Projects, 1961-2000, Series 6:; (Boxes 35-40, 54-55; 5.2 linear feet)